freegamesinc.com 2015-06-07

# Ideal Internet

Ideal Internet, Inc. we appreciates our relationship with you, respects that your information is yours, and is committed to safeguarding your privacy when you’re using [Ideal Internet Inc site(s)](http://www.idealinternet.com/products.html). The following describes our collection of and use of any information that we may collect from you.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

Questions  
If you have any questions, we can be reached via (chris at idealinternet dot com)

We generally do not collect any information.

For each visitor to our Site(s), our web server does not recognize any information regarding the visitor’s domain or e-mail address. We only collect information that you voluntarily provide to us.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable us to recognize your computer and to deliver personalized features. The information collected by cookies is sometimes called “clickstream” or “click trail” and may also describe which areas of the Site you have used. We do not use cookies at this time. However, in the course of serving advertisements to this Site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We do not receive any such information from our third party advertisers nor do we have any control over such third party advertisers or the use of any such information that is collected.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml

**We may amend this Privacy Policy.**

If in the future this Privacy Policy is amended or updated, you will be subject to this Privacy Policy as amended or updated. We will not notify you of any amendments or updates to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy often for any changes hereto.

**copyright 2008/2010 Ideal Internet, Inc. All Rights Reserved.**

**Warning** : include(../sidebar.php): failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/var/www/html/sites/idealinternet.com/idealinternet.com/page/privacy.php** on line **31**  
  
**Warning** : include(): Failed opening '../sidebar.php' for inclusion (include_path='.:/usr/share/pear:/usr/share/php') in **/var/www/html/sites/idealinternet.com/idealinternet.com/page/privacy.php** on line **31**
